What?
I can hear it.
A smoker's cries.
forgotten by a harsh
word, then let it be so.
Upon this world, I shall rain down tar
and ash, for I am the devil of nicotine.
Cockroaches, this floor
is covered in trash.
How could someone even
live in this filth? Hm?
A rotten ball of rice that needs to soak.
Don't they know you have to wash
your dishes after using them?
This is the kind of behavior
that I can't stand. Son of hells!
Was that black goop supposed
to be soup at some point?
Did it just move right now?
Ah! The answer bomb!
I just stepped in something!
It was squishy and now
it's all over my foot!
This place is gross!
I'm done!
I hate this place!
I'm getting the fuck out of here!
Nia
I wanna ask you this, but I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry about moving on my hand,
but it doesn't seem like my hand.
Thank You, such a great
favour, come and say it.
Why can't you say it?
Let's go!
If we experience the better end,
we need to work without grief!
We won't have enough time,
so we remember.
Thanks for the tip about this
temp agency yaku score when
one blows past one cigarette's
budget one gets to work.
Number 82.
You got any work you've
come to the right place.
When can you get started
like yesterday and
find me something that
makes a ton of dough?
Well then, you're in luck.
I've got an opening for
something this afternoon.
As long as it pays great, I'm in.
It's just a simple cleaning job.
Pretty sure anyone can do it.
All right, everyone, 15-minute break.
15 minutes, everyone can come on up.
Hey!
You smell that shit you're covered in?
It's flammable.
I mean, it's no smoking.
I know baseball for dumb, but
you understand that, right?
I really can't stand this fucking job!
They work us like crazy, we don't get
breaks, and on top of that, the pay sucks!
Hey, you, you agree with me, right?
Come on! Me?
Hell yeah, it sucks, right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
Oh!
Autumn Darter's out already?
Well, fall's here, I guess. Goodness.
The older I get, the faster time flies.
Huh?
Hey there, Yaku.
You got back in a hurry.
Hey.
I expected you to take a proper vacation.
Yeah, I wish.
My new part-time gig starts tomorrow.
Anyway, this is for you.
A tasty souvenir.
Oh, look at you. That's nice.
Near my parents' house,
there's a famous dorayaki shop.
I was just about to put the kettle on.
Want a cup of tea?
Sounds nice.
But, uh, I'm a little tired from the
travel, so I'll take a rain check.
Well, all right.
Getting plenty of rest, then. Thanks.
Huh?
Wait, was that Yaku just now?
It sure was.
Come to think of it, I
haven't seen her for a while.
She went back home for a bit.
Anniversary of her granddad's passing.
Now the black hair makes sense.
That black hair looks really cute on her.
I wonder if her grandfather
was beast folk, too.
Huh?
Little red dragonfly,
little red dragonfly.
Da-ba-da-ba-ba, da-da-ba,
little red dragonfly,
I'll cook you up a side dish for
tonight's dinner, little red dragonfly.
Hmm? Hmm?
Nyah!
I'm out of smokes already!
Oh, I know!
Hey, Yaku!
Are you back in town yet, or what?
Got any smokes I can have?
Mm-uh.
Here, kitty-kitty, I know you're in here.
Can I bum a cig or ten off ya?
Yeah.
What is it?
You gotta have one to spare.
What are you doing in the dark?
Why not turn on a light?
In my bag.
Just help yourself.
You should go see your family sometime.
You really should.
Hey, Yanni.
Why why why humans
you're not a human.
So Yaniko how have things been going?
Yeah well uh I've been working
here and there you know.
I've been fired a whole
bunch though really now.
Yeah you'd be my fave
if you had a lighter of
course okay then where
did I put that lighter?
Oh.
I'll borrow a few of these.
I always found it tasted
different when lit with a match.
Yeah
Hey, do you have a spare one for me?
No.
Oh, you're the best. Yeah.
I gotta get through these quick.
So good.
It's this late already?
Oh, no, oh, no.
I'll be home any minute.
Hi, Mom, I'm home.
Hey, what are you doing here?
And you're smoking you
know you can't do that
here how many times do i have to tell you?
Yeah And you just letting her do it mom
doesn't help she's like
this because you never
yell at her I guess when
you promised to quit
the other day that was
lie number one thousand
That face won't work on me yeah
i don't even know what that
face means Like two peas in a
pod no matter how old they get
One movie ticket for Mom.
And one for Big Sis. Yeah.
Movie theaters have assigned seats now.
I love it, too.
Why did you reserve my seat so far away?
Do you have cigarettes with you?
Well, now you know why.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
She likes to act strict,
but look at how Imoko's being
considerate so that you can smoke.
Underneath it all you
can really tell how much
she loves her big sis
we don't need your input
mom the average human
lifespan is around 80 years
I'd be happy if I could
survive for half of that
Toshi I'm begging you
don't be like me I don't
know if I've ever wanted
to smoke so bad you've
got your whole why does
this The movie have to
have so many damn scenes
where they're smoking!
You're anything I've ever wanted to be!
Anyway...
I'm gonna run to the restroom and...
Yes, sir.
Listen, when things don't go
your way, no matter how tough...
Yanniko, I just want one little puff!
Laugh it off.
I will, Yaniko, I will!
No!
Devon, one last run!
Let me go, Yaniko!
Man, I love a good cry during a movie!
I really appreciate you
guys coming with me when
all of my friends found out
this was a yakuza movie.
They had other things to do
Why are you two being weird?
Great now you've got mom smelling
like a gross ashtray, too
Know how to be considerate.
Yeah, I'm not sure I like being
automatically blamed here.
Oh, we're playing the victim game now Oh,
you don't understand
what I don't understand?
Sometimes I wish moments like
these could last forever!
Okay, let's talk about
your recent health checkup.
It's a bit concerning.
The nurse told me your convulsions
made it difficult to draw blood,
which tells me we're
dealing with alcoholism.
Not only are your AST
levels highly elevated,
The score is the inverse
of your current GPA.
I've never seen such a
textbook example of a slacker.
I'm sure you've heard all this before.
Stop the drinking and get back in school.
If not, you won't see your
graduation, but your funeral.
Your funeral. Your funeral.
That was after quitting
for a whole week already.
Look out!
Hey!
Not watching where you're
going is a good way to get hit.
I guess I should go easy on her.
She looks like she's in middle school.
Hey, are you trying to get home?
Yeah.
I'd be happy to walk you
home if you need me to.
This is the same way to
get to Yanni's apartment.
Did something bad happen today?
Yeah.
Yeah, a problem with school.
I've been there.
It's definitely not easy.
Back when I was around your age,
I got bullied in school too.
Not a lot, but I remember it.
Boys would hide my things
like my shoes and recorder.
They'd call me names like Cat Girl.
But then, during middle school graduation,
the head bully confessed something to me.
He told me he did all that
stuff because he liked me.
I couldn't believe it.
I went through all that pain
just because he had a crush.
And that's when I got it.
It was a way bigger deal
in my head than a real.
That story sounds more like a humble brag.
Oh no, I didn't mean it that way.
But I see how you'd think that.
It wasn't intentional.
I just.
I'm just kidding.
I do feel a little better.
My problems aren't as
bad as I think they are.
I'm being dramatic.
I'll get over it.
Oh, I'm glad.
What a strange little girl.
She kind of reminds me of Yanni in a way.
Oh, an earthquake.
Now that's a whole lot of trembling.
I'm over it.
This thing is longer than the
credits at the end of a movie.
Hey, Arto, we best cadattled just in case.
Hold up.
You're causing this?
It's just that I've got a follow-up
appointment coming up from my...
Well, doll, I'm not your mama, but a
little moderation wouldn't hurt you none.
How long since you had a drink?
A day? That's it?
Not really.
It's only been an hour. Come on, Aru.
Time to give it up.
Well, I'm stuck.
Outside of my apartment.
Quake?
It's a biggie.
Rule number one, don't stay indoors.
Can't get it off.
It's gone into spasm mode!
Desperate times!
Desperate measures!
And here we are.
Damn door is stuck and it won't open!
Which means I'm fucking screwed.
Those girls cannot see me like this!
That's rule number two!
I'll go to the balcony door,
round back, and break the glass!
Yeah!
If I've got to choose between
embarrassment and broken glass, no contest.
Hunkin! Huh?
Um, oh, uh, good afternoon.
Wow, is that a centaur costume? How fun.
Oh, wait, maybe not.
I mean, centaurs don't
have two heads, right?
Oh, is this like a Cerberus
variant or something?
Just kill me. Huh?
I don't think I could talk
my way out of this one.
So today I die.
Whoa, whoa, now let's
just calm down a sec here.
Okay then, this is just at the top
of my head, but I'm thinking...
You were in the middle of banging your
bespoke sex doll when the earthquake hit,
but the doll was in vaginal spasm mode
and locked you and your you-know-what in,
so you ran for safety, but you got
locked out, and now you're stuck outside.
I'm gonna guess by the
amount of sweat I'm seeing...
Bullseye!
Monk Art is for the win!
Listen, just hang out in my place
until the handyman gets here, okay?
Well, let me go buy you some underwear.
I'll be apologizing for
the rest of my life.
You don't have to walk that close to me.
So sorry.
Damn, that was close.
Yanni Neko's movements can be hard to
read, so I just had to take her out.
Yeah, hold on.
When did I lay down to take a nap?
You're in my whack-ass dream. Really?
Yeah, you had turned into a censor.
What the fuck are you talking about?
So you wrote something new
you want me to look at?
Please!
Oh, well actually He was
a friend who wrote it.
I haven't posted any of
my writing on Kakeyome.
Based on what you said last time, I
decided to use a popular plot cliche.
that's all over the site.
I mean, that's what my friend decided
to do when she heard your advice.
So you wrote a banishment story?
Yes, exactly.
And it was surprisingly fun, actually.
I realized following a
plot cliche isn't so bad.
I mean, that's what my friend said.
There once was a man
who was a dragon major.
The man had no name,
For he had abandoned it,
nor did he need it as the
people simply called him Major.
A Dragon Major is one of the many vocations
practiced by the peoples of this world.
You're a big fan of
exposition, aren't you?
What's up with this kind of lore so
important for the world building?
Hey, Major.
About time you got here.
Remember you said you wanted
to talk about something?
Listen, kid, I'll be straight with you.
You are no longer a
member of our party. Huh?
Now get off of my ship.
Wait, this major dude is supposed
to be the main character, I guess?
Uh, yeah, that's not bad, is it?
What's wrong?
Why is the main character
the one doing the banishing?
You got it backwards, dude.
Huh? Oh, really?
Oh, I... What?
I... I... Oops.
Of course, I know that's not
what the plot usually goes,
but I didn't want to write the same
thing as everyone else on the Black Wolf.
I thought if I had the
major do the banishing,
then the readers would start
to question the cliche?
and then there would be even
more value added to the story.
any of the cliché stories
on here, have you?
Chainsmoker Cat.
I don't know how you ended up here,
but I get that you're in a bind.
The typhoon blew your tent away,
and I'm sure that makes it
tough to live by the river, huh?
Do you have family at all?
Someone you can reach out to?
Blood ties are nothing
more than a concept,
a way to enforce standards of
relationships. Come on, now.
Now that's not what I mean.
Here's the thing.
You can relax.
I'm not asking you to leave.
It's not like you and I are strangers.
You could even say
we're a family of sorts.
I feel that way about everyone here.
F-family?
Having said that, you can open up to me.
Tell me what's going on.
I'm sure I can find a little corner
that I can rent to you super cheap.
Uh, I would really appreciate that.
Well, I'm glad we worked that out.
Why don't we grab a treat?
It'll be my treat. Yeah.
Whoa, there's that wind!
Kevin! Iora!
Wow!
Uh, sorry about that. Boner!
No, no, look, it's a natural
physiological response for a man!
I can't control it!
I swear! Boner! I can't help it!
I'm sorry, we're a family, right?
We're in this together!
Family?
Boner!
Family members shouldn't
give you a raging boner!
So, whatever comes off,
comes off, right? You got it.
Counting on ya.
Well, alright, here we go.
Whoa, wow, I barely brushed
it and look at all this.
I mean, it is shedding season, isn't it?
Look at how much fur I've brushed out.
It's like clockwork,
every spring and fall.
I can't believe how much is coming off.
I feel like I could make another
Yanni Neko out of all this.
I'm really enjoying this, this is so fun.
I don't know.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
We had relate or work too.
And are BEC.
Speaking of people in the street?
I know I know, I don't care.
I'm going to be happy.
And I'm still there.
I have no doubt.
There are siren.
Thank you.